[ RADIO TUNING ]
[ SIRENS ]
[ RADIO ] Now we need to talk about another type of violence .
[ RADIO ] It 's the trouble between supporters of Palmeiras and Corinthians .
[ RADIO ] yesterday afternoon .
[ RADIO ] They fought outside the stadium ,
[ RADIO ] and the police had to intervene .
[ RADIO ] Our team recorded tragic scenes of violence .
[ RADIO ] And we 've heard a Palmeiras supporter .
[ RADIO ] was stabbed to death yesterday in the fight with the other team .
[ BLOW ] [ VALDIR ] For fuck 's sake , Capela !
[ CAPELA ] The road is badly painted . How am I going to see ?
[ VALDIR ] What time is it ?
[ CAPELA ] You 're so lazy . Can 't you see I 'm driving ?
[ CAPELA ] It 's 2 : 40 a.m. [ VALDIR ] Let 's go to the morgue .
[ CAPELA ] C 'mon , man . I 'm starving . Let 's have lunch .
[ VALDIR ] There 's a lot of blood , Capela ! Take us to the morgue !
[ SIRENS ]
SUSPENSE MUSIC
[ CAPELA ] Is this the turkey carwash ?
[ LAUGHTER ]
[ CAPELA ] This one doesn 't gobble anymore . It 's cool .
[ CAPELA ] GouvÃ © a won 't need to cut him open so much .
[ STENIO ] He 's like swiss cheese . [ VALDIR ] He 's a Palmeiras supporter .
[ VALDIR ] He 's fumigated .
[ CAPELA ] Well , gentleman , I 'm calling it a day .
[ CAPELA ] StÃ © nio , wash this turkey well . [ STENIO ] Just go , Capela . Go .
[ STENIO ] Go because someone is doing overtime on your wife .
[ CAPELA ] Hey ! [ STENIO ] Go !
[ STENIO ] You had a fight because of soccer , right ?
[ STENIO ] How classy !
[ STENIO ] Didn 't you think about your family ?
[ VALDECIR ] Is this the hospital ?
[ STENIO ] This is the end of the line .
[ STENIO ] You 've gone to the other side . I 'm sorry .
[ VALDECIR ] What do you mean the other side , man ?
[ VALDECIR ] I 'm going back to the bar .
[ VALDECIR ] That stupid drunk wanted to screw with me .
[ VALDECIR ] I 'll mess him up .
[ STENIO ] You 're not going anywhere .
[ STENIO ] It 's over .
[ VALDECIR ] So ...
[ VALDECIR ] Is this it ?
[ VALDECIR ] I have a family , man .
[ VALDECIR ] Call them , man .
[ VALDECIR ] I don 't want to be buried as a hobo , for the love of God !
[ STENIO ] Easy , easy , easy .
[ STENIO ] Tell me . What 's your name ?
[ STENIO ] Good morning , I 'd like to speak to Ms. Edma .
[ STENIO ] Ms. Edma , I 'm calling about your husband ,
[ STENIO ] Mr. Valdecir .
[ STENIO ] My name is StÃ © nio .
[ STENIO ] I work in the coroner 's office .
[ RADIO ] I call the power authority in the name of Jesus .
[ RADIO ] I demand the evil leave .
[ RADIO ] I say , " Disease , go away !
[ RADIO ] Rheumatism , go away ! "
[ STENIO ] Hilda , put it there for me , please .
[ STENIO ] Hilda , could you give me one more , please ?
[ JAIME ] Today you have to read the sign .
[ STENIO ] I get paid on Thursday . I 'll pay you later .
[ JAIME ] I want to improve the level of clients here .
[ JAIME ] But for you , just for you ,
[ JAIME ] I 'll allow it one last time .
[ STENIO ] You don 't need to say it like that .
[ JAIME ] We open at 5 : 00 , did you forget ?
[ LARA ] Dad , I took 3 buses from the hospital .
[ LARA ] Hi , Hilda . [ HILDA ] Oi .
[ JAIME ] Once in a while is okay , but you 're always coming in late .
[ JAIME ] You should go there sometime .
[ JAIME ] I let Nora go , remember ? I need you .
[ JAIME ] You don 't need to go there every day .
[ LARA ] It 's not right leaving her so alone .
[ JAIME ] For the love of God , she doesn 't even know you 're there .
[ JAIME ] Lara .
[ JAIME ] Here . Go .
[ MINISTER ON THE RADIO ]
[ CARTOON SOUNDS ]
[ STENIO ] Hi , you .
[ CICA ] Hi .
[ STENIO ] Where 's the little hand on my head ?
[ STENIO ] Where is everyone ?
[ CICA ] They 're inside . Edson got in trouble .
[ ODETE ] StÃ © nio , get up from there .
[ ODETE ] I told you not to lie there in your dirty work clothes !
[ ODETE ] It stinks up the couch !
[ ODETE ] Do you know what this is ?
[ ODETE ] This is kite wire . It cuts like a knife .
[ ODETE ] Who 's making it ? Your son .
[ ODETE ] To sell to the boys and steal kites .
[ ODETE ] I almost had to go to the police station ...
[ ODETE ] What are you doing ? You 're grounded . Go inside !
[ EDSON ] Crap . [ STENIO ] Boy , come back here .
[ ODETE ] Do you see how they are ? This one is rude , too .
[ ODETE ] You see how they talk to me ? You won 't do anything ?
[ STENIO ] I 'll do something . Later . Later .
[ STENIO ] I 'll do something . I 'll talk to him in a while .
[ STENIO ] I 'll take a shower first . I 'm tired .
[ ODETE ] The smell stays . Everything smells bad .
[ ODETE ] This smell from work ... Let me see .
[ ODETE ] Go wash your hands . [ CICA ] Mom ...
[ ODETE ] Cica , go wash your hands . Smell it to see if you like it .
[ ODETE SINGING ]
[ ODETE SINGING ] When our love comes back time and again
[ HUMMING ]
[ WHISTLING ]
[ ODETE ] You 're going to be late .
[ STENIO ] I worked late yesterday .
[ ODETE ] Leave me alone . I 'm not in the mood today .
[ RADIO SINGING ] When our love comes back time and again .
[ GOUVEA ] I 'm going , StÃ © nio .
[ GOUVEA ] Finish sewing him up ,
[ GOUVEA ] give the man a bath and put him in the freezer .
[ GOUVEA ] And try to get some rest , okay ?
[ STENIO ] Alright . See you tomorrow , GouvÃ © a .
[ STENIO ] Did the police catch you ?
[ STENIO ] Relax , man . I 'm not a cop .
[ STENIO ] Where are you from ?
[ SUJO ] Cidade Tiradentes . The ROTA did me .
[ STENIO ] What 's your name ?
[ SUJO ] Sujo . [ STENIO ] Sujo ?
[ STENIO ] Do you work for Gilvan ? [ SUJO ] What Gilvan , man ?
[ SUJO ] I 'm Jonas ' brother . Why do you ask ?
[ STENIO ] Relax , dude . I see a lot of dead crooks here .
[ STENIO ] You did time , right ?
[ SUJO ] How do you know ?
[ STENIO ] This tattoo here . It says , " CDP is 13 . "
[ SUJO ] You know too much . Who 's been talking to you ?
[ STENIO ] Tchaco , Tocha , Matheus .
[ SUJO ] These guys died in a shooting with the police .
[ SUJO ] But me ... I was backstabbed .
[ STENIO ] Someone rat on you ?
[ SUJO ] It was Dentinho .
[ SUJO ] Bastard .
[ SUJO ] Bro , can you help me out at Divineia ?
[ SUJO ] For the love of God . My brother is death personified .
[ SUJO ] He 'll give that fucker Dentinho what he deserves .
[ STENIO ] No way .
[ STENIO ] If I tell them what you tell me ,
[ STENIO ] bad things can happen .
[ SUJO ] You 're the last voice I 'm hearing before Satan .
[ SUJO ] Did you know ? [ STENIO ] Are you crazy , bro ?
[ STENIO ] Bite your tongue .
[ SUJO ] I killed my dad .
[ SUJO ] Me and Jonas .
[ SUJO ] That fucking old man . He used to hit our mother .
[ SUJO ] We stabbed him three times in the chest .
[ SUJO ] And threw him off a bridge in Registro .
[ SUJO ] Only we and God know .
[ SUJO ] God doesn 't forgive those who Kill their families .
TENSE MUSIC
[ ODETE ] C 'mon , mister . You can come in .
[ ODETE ] Careful not to rip my couch on that hook on the wall !
[ ODETE ] The entrance is on the side . Come this way .
[ STENIO ] What the fuck ? What the hell ?
[ STENIO ] Wait ... Who bought that ?
[ STENIO ] Man , leave the couch there . [ ODETE ] No , mister . Take it in .
[ STENIO ] Who bought that , Odete ? [ ODETE ] I did . You wouldn 't .
[ STENIO ] I work hard to pay rent , and you buy this in secret ?
[ ODETE ] I paid with my work . [ STENIO ] What work , Odete ?
[ ODETE ] The sweets I help Doraci make !
[ STENIO ] That 's a lot of sweets to pay for this fucking couch .
[ ODETE ] Take the couch in . [ STENIO ] Wait , wait .
[ ODETE ] It 's an installment plan . [ STENIO ] An installment plan ?
[ STENIO ] I 'm going to end up paying ! [ ODETE ] What are you paying , StÃ © nio ?
[ ODETE ] I 've had it with you . I 've really had it with you .
[ ODETE ] Your life doesn 't improve . You don 't treat me well .
[ ODETE ] And your smell stinks up my house .
[ ODETE ] You 're disgusting . I 'm disgusted by you .
[ ODETE ] Disgusted by you .
[ ODETE ] Let 's go , mister . Take the couch in .
[ DOCTOR ] Check the IV . Larissa , clean the catheter .
[ DOCTOR ] Take care of the access . Bring the monitor .
[ DOCTOR ] Lara ...
[ LARA ] Did something happen ?
[ DOCTOR ] She had a cardiac arrest .
[ DOCTOR ] We 're taking her to the ICU .
[ DEEP BREATHING ]
[ CRYING ]
[ VALDIR ] C 'mon , c 'mon . [ CAPELA ] Go blow , go blow .
[ LAUGHTER ]
[ BLOW ]
[ YELLING ]
[ LAUGHTER ]
[ STENIO ] Fucking stupid joke , Valdir .
[ STENIO ] Don 't you have anything better to do ? [ LAUGHTER ]
[ STENIO ] And you , Capela ? Did you forget to take your pill ?
[ STENIO ] Or did you jerk off in the bathroom ?
[ STENIO ] Take your hands off me ! [ VALDIR ] Stop it ! What the fuck , man ?
[ VALDIR ] It was just a joke .
[ CAPELA ] Can 't you take a joke ? [ STENIO ] What kind of joke is that ?
[ LAUGHTER ]
[ VALDIR ] You liked it , right ?
[ CARLAO ] You had to see your face when you saw my cock , StÃ © nio .
[ CARLAO ] StÃ © nio ...
[ STENIO ] Do I know you , asshole ?
[ CARLAO ] Vila Gustavo in the house , brother !
[ STENIO ] Fuck , right on my shift !
[ CARLAO ] StÃ © nio , you 're talking to the dead now ?
[ CARLAO ] Dude , I 'm going to piss in your ear .
[ STENIO ] What did you do ? [ CARLAO ] I was stealing hearts .
[ STENIO ] From other people 's girls .
[ STENIO ] When you mess around , you go to the other side early .
[ STENIO ] I feel sorry for your mother . [ CARLAO ] Have you no respect , crook ?
[ STENIO ] Crook ? All the crooks end up on this gurney .
[ CARLAO ] Yeah ? [ STENIO ] I have to stitch you up later .
[ CARLAO ] Do you know why ? Because you 're a loser .
[ CARLAO ] Unlike me , who enjoyed life the way God wanted ,
[ CARLAO ] better than you .
[ CARLAO ] While you 're washing dead people ,
[ CARLAO ] your wife is cheating on you , boy .
[ STENIO ] What did you say ?
[ DOOR CREAKING ]
[ GOUVEA ] Hey , StÃ © nio .
[ GOUVEA ] Is everything ready ? [ STENIO ] I just need to wash the table .
[ GOUVEA ] Hurry up then . I 'm getting a coffee .
[ STENIO ] What was that , Carlao ? You 're talking about my wife !
[ CARLAO ] Now you 're mad , right , loser ?
[ CARLAO ] You should take it out on the right guy .
[ CARLAO ] I doubt you 'll get tough like this with Jaime .
[ STENIO ] Jaime from the store ? [ CARLAO ] That 's him , man .
[ CARLAO ] You know nothing about women , StÃ © nio .
[ CARLAO ] Don 't you notice her clothes ? Who do you think pays for that ?
[ STENIO ] Shut up !
[ CARLAO ] StÃ © nio ! StÃ © nio !
[ CARLAO ] Come back , StÃ © nio !
[ OFFICER ] When we got there , we saw three boys on the ground .
[ OFFICER ] It was a mess .
[ JAIME ] Wow ... And the parents ?
[ OFFICER ] A bunch of bums . [ JAIME ] One second .
[ JAIME ] Ten reals .
[ STENIO ] I have no money , Mr. Jaime . Can I pay you tomorrow ?
[ JAIME ] I can 't let you .
[ JAIME ] You haven 't paid what you owe me .
[ STENIO ] You 're really doing this to me , Mr. Jaime ?
[ JAIME ] My store is not a cachaca welfare station .
[ OFFICER ] Is everything okay , Mr. Jaime ?
[ JAIME ] Don 't you have anything ? A check , a watch , a cell phone ?
[ JAIME ] Let me check this .
[ JAIME ] You need to raise the level , StÃ © nio .
[ MUSIC ON THE RADIO ]
[ HONK ]
She 's going to get some bread for breakfast .
[ STENIO PANTING ]
[ TV ] My family has always given me selfesteem .
[ TV ] and there was always a political thinking .
[ TV ] in the places I went .
[ TV ] We need to understand the context we live in .
[ TV ] and how we can contribute to improve the situation .
[ TV ] My family was crucial to me .
[ TV ] They were affectionate and gave me selfesteem .
[ ODETE ] I was watching that . Put it back .
[ ODETE ] Go watch TV in the bedroom .
[ ODETE ] What is this ? Why are you sitting on the floor ?
[ STENIO ] I want to watch the news . It 's my house .
[ ODETE ] Okay ...
[ ODETE ] You want to watch the news . It 's your house .
[ ODETE ] Then you sit here watching the news .
[ ODETE ] I 'm going to the bedroom to forget you exist .
[ ODETE ] Why don 't you cook for the kids and take them to school ?
[ ODETE ] Since it 's your house .
[ TV ] ... when heavily armed men got there .
[ TV ] and started shooting .
[ TV ] The battle was between two rival gangs .
[ TV ] who fight for drug traffic control in this area .
[ TV ] The group led by Gilvan Barreiro .
[ TV ] and the rival gang , commanded by Jonas Cravo .
[ TV ] The reason seems to be revenge for the death .
[ TV ] of Jonas ' brother , Manuel Cravo , Sujo .
[ STENIO ] Sujo ...
[ TV ] The area is under ...
SUSPENSE MUSIC
[ STENIO ] Hey , bro .
[ STENIO ] I want to talk to Jonas .
[ GUY ] I don 't know any Jonas .
[ STENIO ] I know who ratted on Sujo .
[ JAIME ] Thank you .
[ ODETE ] I 'm loving , you don 't like it . I do whatever . You don 't like it .
[ ODETE ] Don 't you answer your phone anymore ?
[ JAIME ] Do you want 6 loaves of bread ?
[ JAIME ] I didn 't see my phone . [ ODETE ] You haven 't seen it all day ?
[ JAIME ] Not here . [ ODETE ] This is weird . What 's up ?
[ NOISE ] [ JAIME ] Don 't touch that !
[ JAIME ] We 'll talk later . [ ODETE ] What time ?
[ LARA ] Hi , Edson . [ EDSON ] Hi , Lara .
[ ODETE ] In the corner at 8pm . Sharp . [ JAIME ] Okay ! Go away .
[ LARA ] I went to your school , too .
[ ODETE ] Let 's go . No , not that . Disgusting !
[ ODETE ] Nothing with sugar . Let 's go , let 's go .
[ ODETE ] What ? What are you looking at ?
[ ODETE ] This is where I want to live . In house number 80 .
[ BARKING ]
[ MAN ] This is the guy , boss .
[ JONAS ] Where did you know Sujo from ?
[ STENIO ] I did time with him in CDP .
[ STENIO ] I 'm StÃ © nio .
[ JONAS ] He never mentioned you . [ STENIO ] No ?
[ STENIO ] He talked about you a lot .
[ STENIO ] He 'd say Jonas was the only real daredevil he knew .
[ STENIO ] in the East Zone .
[ JONAS ] Dentinho ,
[ JONAS ] go get a beer and nice bunch of weed .
[ JONAS ] for our guest .
[ JONAS ] We 're going to talk .
[ JONAS ] Tell me . What do you know ?
[ JONAS ] Who ratted on my brother to the ROTA ?
[ STENIO ] I have a friend who works in the morgue .
[ STENIO ] He 's friends with the pigs .
[ STENIO ] He told me when the ROTA delivered Sujo 's body there .
[ STENIO ] He told me who the rat was .
[ JONAS ] Tell me .
[ STENIO ] It 's a guy from Vila Gustavo .
[ JONAS ] Vila Gustavo ?
[ STENIO ] Yeah . He had some mess with Sujo .
[ STENIO ] His name is Jaime .
[ STENIO ] He has a bakery on the corner of Juarez Dagoberto .
[ JONAS ] Are you sure ?
[ STENIO ] One hundred percent .
[ JONAS ] I 'm a crook , man . But I 'm not a psychopath .
[ JONAS ] You should know that anyone who tricks me doesn 't live .
[ STENIO ] With all due respect ,
[ STENIO ] to do what you and Sujo did to defend and protect your mom ,
[ STENIO ] you can only be an honored and correct guy .
[ JONAS ] That was between me and Sujo !
[ STENIO ] Sujo was my brother .
[ STENIO ] This rat from the store .
[ STENIO ] deserves to die like your deceased father .
[ STENIO ] Stabbed three times in the chest and thrown from the bridge .
[ JONAS ] You said it , so it 's an order .
[ JONAS ] Go with him .
[ MOANING ]
[ ODETE ] What is it ?
[ JAIME ] Nothing . Seeing your kids ' names isn 't easy .
[ SIGHING ]
[ JAIME ] And taking the kids to the store was a low blow .
[ STENIO ] Two , three .
[ STENIO ] Go with God , Carlao .
[ STENIO ] Talk to me , Carlao .
[ CARLAO ] You 're fucked , StÃ © nio .
[ CARLAO ] Why did you do this shit ?
[ CARLAO ] A dead man 's secret is a death secret , StÃ © nio .
[ CARLAO ] Now you 're marked , brother .
[ STENIO ] Marked ? [ MAN ] What ?
[ STENIO ] No , no ...
[ STENIO ] Help me with the lid .
TENSE MUSIC
[ DENTINHO ] Boss , the rat is here .
[ JONAS ] Follow him .
[ DENTINHO ] Boss , there 's a woman with him .
[ JAIME SIGHS ]
[ JAIME ] Do you need anything ?
[ ODETE ] Yes . Yes , I do .
[ ODETE ] I need peace and quiet .
[ ODETE ] I need two babysitters , one for each kid .
[ JAIME ] Odete ...
[ JAIME ] We need to slow it down .
[ JAIME ] The vibe is weird . I think StÃ © nio knows everything .
[ ODETE ] What are you talking about , Jaime ?
[ JAIME ] He went to the store and made a scene there .
[ JAIME ] He wanted to pay later . The way he looked at me ...
[ JAIME ] I 'm sure he knows about everything .
[ ODETE ] Oh , no . No , Jaime , don 't do this to me .
[ ODETE ] My life is a disgrace .
[ JAIME ] I can 't , Odete .
[ JAIME ] Do me a favor ? Give him his phone back ...
[ ODETE ] I want him dead ! [ JAIME ] Stop that !
[ ODETE ] I 'll divorce him ... What is this ? Oh my God !
[ JAIME ] Easy , easy ! [ DENTINHO ] Get out , motherfucker !
[ ODETE ] Easy , mister . [ JAIME ] I 'm coming out . Easy .
[ ODETE ] Jesus ! [ DENTINHO ] On your knees !
[ JAIME ] For the love of God , take that gun out of my head .
[ JONAS ] Do you know why you 're going to die ?
[ JONAS ] Jaime , right ? [ ODETE ] Mister , put that gun down !
[ DENTINHO ] Shut up ! Shut up !
[ JONAS ] I 'm Sujo 's brother , asshole ! [ JAIME ] Who ?
[ THUD ] [ SCREAM ]
[ JONAS ] You know who , you stupid rat .
[ JONAS ] My brother died because of you .
[ JONAS ] You 're going to the same place . You messed with the devil !
[ JAIME ] Please , I don 't know your brother .
[ JAIME ] Put that gun away , for the love of God .
[ JONAS ] You want me to put it away ? I 'll do it . I don 't want to use it .
[ JONAS ] This is how my brother died .
[ JONAS ] Just like this , kneeling in front of the ROTA .
[ JAIME ] I don 't know your brother . You can take the car .
[ JONAS ] The car ? I don 't want the car !
[ JONAS ] I want something else .
[ JONAS ] I want to see the street drink your blood .
[ CRYING ]
TENSE MUSIC
[ ODETE ] My God ...
[ ODETE ] You murderer ! You coward !
[ JONAS ] Go home , woman . Forget our faces . Go home .
[ ODETE ] The police .
[ ODETE ] They called the cops on you !
[ ODETE ] You 're going down ! The cops will arrest you !
[ DENTINHO ] Jonas , wrap it up . The police are coming !
[ JONAS ] Shut up , man ! [ ODETE ] Jonas ? You murderer !
[ ODETE ] Your name is Jonas ! They 'll catch you !
[ ODETE ] You 're all going down !
[ GUNSHOT ]
[ DENTINHO ] Let 's go , boss .
[ SIRENS ]
[ LOUD NOISE ]
[ DORACI ] StÃ © nio ...
[ DORACI ] My God , StÃ © nio ! Something tragic happened !
[ DORACI ] It 's Odete , StÃ © nio !
[ STENIO ] Odete .
[ STENIO ] Odete !
[ STENIO ] Get out of the way ! Move !
[ STENIO ] Out of the way ! Odete ! Move ! Out of the way !
[ STENIO ] Odete ! Move ! Move ! Odete ! Odete !
[ STENIO ] Odete ...
[ STENIO ] It 's my wife ! [ OFFICER ] Easy ...
[ STENIO ] What did they do to you ?
[ ODETE ] My son ! Don 't let him see me like this !
[ ODETE ] StÃ © nio , for the love of God , get him out of here .
[ STENIO ] My son ... Don 't let him through .
[ EDSON ] Dad , Dad ... Mom ! Mom ! Mom ...
[ STENIO ] Easy , son . [ EDSON ] It 's my mom , Dad !
[ EDSON ] Dad ! It 's my mom !
TENSE MUSIC
[ ODETE ] So you can hear me ?
[ ODETE ] How ?
[ STENIO ] I always have .
[ STENIO ] I 've always talked with dead people .
[ STENIO ] With you , with Carlao , who ended up here .
[ STENIO ] I talk with the dead .
[ STENIO ] I can 't explain it .
[ ODETE ] Do the children know about me ?
[ ODETE ] Look , StÃ © nio ...
[ ODETE ] I was getting up the courage to tell you about Jaime .
[ STENIO ] But the truth was quicker than your respect .
[ STENIO ] But I won 't die like you .
[ STENIO ] I 'm not going to be Vila Gustavo 's loser .
[ ODETE ] No one knew , StÃ © nio . [ STENIO ] Now everyone knows .
[ STENIO ] But I had the last laugh .
[ STENIO ] I sent the bastard to burn in the fire of hell .
[ STENIO ] I just didn 't know you 'd go down with him .
[ ODETE ] StÃ © nio ...
[ ODETE ] You 're not a part of this , right ? [ STENIO ] What do you think ?
[ ODETE ] You bastard ! Motherfucker !
[ STENIO ] Maybe now you 'll respect me , Odete .
[ ODETE ] How did you dare .
[ ODETE ] to have the mother of your children killed ?
[ ODETE ] They 'll never forgive you . I 'll never forgive you .
[ STENIO ] But I forgive you .
[ STENIO ] Five little stones .
[ STENIO ] One for each letter of your name .
[ STENIO ] You 're going under the dirt , Odete .
[ STENIO ] Mine .
[ ODETE ] What are you doing ? Take this off me !
[ ODETE ] StÃ © nio .
[ ODETE ] StÃ © nio , come back here !
[ ODETE ] StÃ © nio , come back here ! Come back , StÃ © nio !
[ METALLIC NOISE ]
[ THUD ]
[ THUDS ]
[ KNOCKING ON DOOR ]
[ OFFICER ] Good afternoon . Are you this boy 's father ?
[ STENIO ] What a shame , Edson ... What a shame .
[ STENIO ] Is this why I work every night stitching up bodies ?
[ STENIO ] For my son to steal from a market ?
[ STENIO ] Come home as a criminal ?
[ EDSON ] You wanted me to be a loser at school ?
[ STENIO ] You 're a crook then ?
[ STENIO ] Why are you laughing ?
[ STENIO ] Edson , come back . I 'm talking to you , Edson !
[ STENIO ] Edson ! Edson !
[ KNOCKS ] [ STENIO ] Edson , open this door !
[ STENIO ] Open this door , Edson !
[ SILVIO ] What 's up , GouvÃ © a ? [ GOUVEA ] Hey , Silvinho . It 's bad , huh ?
[ SILVIO ] It 's intense , my man . Come see .
[ GOUVEA ] StÃ © nio , grab us some masks .
[ GOUVEA ] Where are the bodies ? [ SILVIO ] There .
[ GOUVEA ] For fuck 's sake ... At this time of night ...
[ FLIES BUZZING ]
[ GOUVEA ] Give us a light .
[ GOUVEA ] By the look of them , they 've been rotting for a while ,
[ GOUVEA ] Fuck ...
[ GOUVEA ] Let 's set it up , StÃ © nio . It 's not going to be easy .
TENSE MUSIC
[ VACUUM CLEANER ]
[ EDSON ] Dad ?
[ EDSON ] It 's nothing . Just sleep . [ CICA ] Are you sure it wasn 't dad ?
[ CICA SCREAMING ]
[ NOISES ]
[ EDSON WHISPERING ] Come on ! Come on !
TENSE MUSIC
[ DOOR SLAMMING ] [ CHILDREN SCREAMING ]
[ SCREAMS ]
[ CICA ] Open it ! Come on ! [ EDSON ] Hang on !
[ EDSON ] Hang on ! Hang on !
[ GOUVEA ] This is weird . Shine a light here , StÃ © nio .
[ GOUVEA ] Look at this . This isn 't normal . Do you see ?
[ STENIO ] It looks like an animal bite .
[ STENIO ] They 've been in the woods for a long time .
[ GOUVEA ] Slow down with your theory .
[ GOUVEA ] If it 's an animal bite ,
[ GOUVEA ] how come it 's only bitten on the inside ?
[ GOUVEA ] There 's nothing on the skin .
[ GOUVEA ] There are no teeth marks on the outside .
[ JONAS ] The bitch killed us both . But it should have been three .
[ JONAS ] You were supposed to be the first one .
[ GOUVEA ] Give me the spacer , StÃ © nio .
[ JONAS ] We Killed two innocent people because of you .
[ JONAS ] The devil came back fierce , you ass .
[ SNAP ]
[ GOUVEA ] What the hell is that ?
SUSPENSE MUSIC
[ GOUVEA ] What is it , StÃ © nio ?
[ COUGHING ]
[ BARKING ] [ VOICES ]
[ STENIO ] Cica ! Edson !
[ KNOCKING ON DOOR ]
[ STENIO ] What are you doing here ?
[ LARA ] Your kids ... [ STENIO ] Where are they ?
[ LARA ] They 're with me . It 's okay .
[ LARA ] They said someone got in here .
[ LARA ] Do they stay alone at night ?
[ STENIO ] Let 's go get them ?
[ LARA ] Do you need any help ?
[ STENIO ] No , thanks . We 'll be okay .
[ STENIO ] We 'll be okay .
[ STENIO ] GouvÃ © a , there are bodies everywhere .
[ STENIO ] In the hall , the kitchen , even in the bathroom !
[ STENIO ] Okay , but ...
[ STENIO ] GouvÃ © a , it 's up to God then .
[ SIRENS ]
[ STENIO ] We need to put bodies on the floor .
[ STENIO ] We have more coming .
[ VALDIR ] You 're joking . [ STENIO ] No , there was another landslide .
[ STENIO ] Let 's do this . Put the gurney there .
[ STENIO ] Come on , Capela .
[ VALDIR ] How are we going to move ? [ STENIO ] I don 't know , man !
[ SIRENS ]
[ VALDIR ] StÃ © nio , you still haven 't finished here ?
[ STENIO ] Wait , man ! Give me a break ! I haven 't gotten there yet .
[ STENIO ] Here , here . You can put them back here .
[ GOUVEA ] StÃ © nio , stop what you 're doing and come help me .
[ STENIO ] GouvÃ © a , I can 't now . [ GOUVEA ] What do you mean ?
[ STENIO ] I 'm cleaning here ! [ GOUVEA ] What ?
[ MAN ] There 's no more space . [ STENIO ] I don 't know ...
[ MAN ] We need to find a way . [ STENIO ] I told you I don 't know !
[ STENIO ] Fucking handle it !
[ VOICES OF THE DEAD ]
[ GOUVEA ] StÃ © nio !
[ GOUVEA ] C 'mon , StÃ © nio . Are you deaf ?
[ VOICES OF THE DEAD ]
[ SIGHING ]
TENSE MUSIC
[ SCREAMS ]
[ LAUGHTER ]
[ SCREAMING ]
[ COUGHING ]
[ VALDIR ] StÃ © nio !
[ VALDIR ] StÃ © nio .
[ CAPELA ] What happened ? [ VALDIR ] The guy is cold !
[ CAPELA ] Were you in there , man ?
[ VALDIR ] Capela , go grab something . [ STENIO ] Who was here ?
[ VALDIR ] Easy , easy . There was no one here .
[ VALDIR ] Fuck , Capela , move ! [ CAPELA ] I 'm going !
[ VALDIR ] Go ! [ COUGHING ]
[ VALDIR ] Stay here .
[ STENIO PANTING ]
[ LARA ] Good morning .
[ CARTOON ON TV ]
[ LARA ] Jesus ... [ CICA ] Dad !
[ LARA ] You 're burning up . He has a fever .
[ LARA ] Help me , Edson . Let 's take him to the bedroom .
[ LARA ] Here .
[ LARA ] I 'm taking the kids to eat . [ STENIO ] You don 't have to .
[ LARA ] StÃ © nio , your children don 't want to be alone anymore .
[ LARA ] They came to my house again . [ STENIO ] Don 't worry .
[ LARA ] My dad didn 't wear cologne . My mom only used good perfumes .
[ STENIO ] Why are you saying that ?
[ LARA ] Odete 's perfume .
[ LARA ] When my mom had the stroke , I took care of the house .
[ LARA ] That 's when the smell started . In his clothes .
[ LARA ] After I smelled it , everything went downhill .
[ LARA ] They killed my dad . I found out I have debts .
[ LARA ] I don 't have the store anymore .
[ LARA ] I might even lose my house .
[ STENIO ] Okay ...
[ STENIO ] I 'm fucked , you 're fucked . Now what ?
[ LARA ] I 'm not my dad . I didn 't harm anyone .
[ STENIO ] What are you going to do now ?
[ LARA ] I 'll handle it . I 'll get a job .
[ STENIO ] You asked me if I needed help with the children .
[ TV NOISE ] The person is looking for comfort ,
[ TV NOISE ] looking for spiritual peace ...
[ BANGING NOISE ]
[ LARA ] Cica .
[ LARA ] Cica , Cica !
[ LARA ] My God ! Cica !
[ LARA ] Cica . My God ...
[ TV ] The power of prayer is stronger .
[ TV ] The power of God has strength .
[ TV ] We 'll show this . Just stay calm . Well done .
[ TV ] I want to know who 's in there . Who 's in there ?
[ TV ] I don 't want to hear about small entities .
[ TV ] You just remain calm .
TENSE MUSIC
I 'M DISGUSTED BY YOU
[ SCREAM ON TV ]
[ TV ] I like raw meat !
[ TV ] And I 'm going to destroy her life !
[ TV ] Do you see , church , what evil can do ?
[ TV ] This kind of evil can be at your house .
[ TV ] But we 're here expurgating and cleansing .
[ TV ] We 're clearing out this place .
[ TV ] When our love comes back .
[ TV ] again and again .
[ TV ] What is it ? What are you looking at ?
[ CAPELA ] They found this in a ditch in Jardim Robru .
[ CAPELA ] With no head or fingerprints to identify it .
[ CAPELA ] The police think he 's a judge the criminals wanted dead .
[ CAPELA ] GouvÃ © a said it was a priority .
[ VALDIR ] This body wasn 't like this . [ GOUVEA ] What do you mean ?
[ GOUVEA ] Valdir , look at this . What time did it come in ?
[ VALDIR ] About 3 hours ago . I helped them bring it .
[ VALDIR ] The body wasn 't like that .
[ STENIO ] What 's going on ?
[ GOUVEA ] Valdir said the body didn 't arrive like this .
[ STENIO ] It didn 't . [ GOUVEA ] The guy 's spine was removed .
[ VALDIR ] The body didn 't come in like this .
[ STENIO ] I received the body . You want to see ?
[ STENIO ] Look , GouvÃ © a . Look at the back .
[ STENIO ] It wasn 't like this . It 's not possible .
[ STENIO ] Look at this one .
[ GOUVEA ] Did anyone else come in here ? [ VALDIR ] No .
[ GOUVEA ] Well ... This doesn 't make any sense .
[ STENIO ] Let 's find it . Let 's go .
[ STENIO ] Fuck ...
[ GOUVEA ] Listen . This body was your responsibility .
[ GOUVEA ] I 'm not dealing with the police , okay ?
[ GOUVEA ] Do what you have to do , but fucking find it .
I 'M DISGUSTED BY YOU
[ STENIO ] It can 't have been Cica .
[ LARA ] But she was holding this .
[ STENIO ] A child couldn 't reach this high .
[ LARA ] I don 't wear lipstick .
[ STENIO ] Lara !
[ STENIO ] I 'm sorry . I wasn 't accusing you .
[ LARA ] It 's okay . I just need to rest .
[ STENIO ] Hi , sweetie .
[ STENIO ] You 're up ? Did you have breakfast ?
[ GIDEAO ] Your wife is buried the way we left her , StÃ © nio .
[ STENIO ] I think someone moved her body , Gideao .
[ STENIO ] When I buried her , she was wearing our wedding ring .
[ STENIO ] And now someone left it at my door .
[ GIDEAO ] If you 're so sure , you need to go to the police .
[ STENIO ] No , Gideao . I 'm desperate . I don 't want to talk to the police .
[ STENIO ] Help me out . I need to see her body .
[ GIDEAO ] Forget that , StÃ © nio . Go home .
[ GIDEAO ] StÃ © nio .
[ GIDEAO ] Tonight the Umbanda guys are coming to do an offering .
[ GIDEAO ] I 'll be with them .
[ GIDEAO ] I can take them far away from her grave .
[ GIDEAO ] If you want to risk it , do it alone , alright ?
TENSE MUSIC
[ STENIO PANTING ]
[ STENIO ] You wanted to talk to me , Odete ?
[ STENIO ] You 're sending me messages . I 'm here . Talk to me .
TENSE MUSIC
[ STENIO ] Odete ...
[ STENIO ] I know I went too far .
[ STENIO ] But Cica and Edson don 't deserve this .
[ ODETE ] Who are you to say who deserves what ?
[ ODETE ] You want forgiveness ?
[ ODETE ] How can I forgive you ?
[ ODETE ] Huh , StÃ © nio ? Tell me .
[ STENIO ] Leave me alone .
[ ODETE ] You thought I was so beautiful ...
[ ODETE ] Look what 's left of me and ask for forgiveness .
TENSE MUSIC
[ THUD ]
[ GROANING ]
[ STENIO PANTING ]
[ GIDEAO ] Over there , you guys !
[ GIDEAO ] StÃ © nio ! Wake up , StÃ © nio ! StÃ © nio , breathe !
[ GIDEAO ] Breathe , StÃ © nio !
[ SIRENS ]
[ CARLAO ] You 're fucked , StÃ © nio . How did you do this shit ?
[ SCREAM ]
[ PANTING ]
[ CICA ] Dad ! [ STENIO ] Hi , sweetie .
[ LARA ] What happened , StÃ © nio ? [ STENIO ] We 'll talk later .
[ CARTOON ON TV ]
[ LARA ] My God , you 're badly hurt .
[ CICA ] Did the police hit you ? [ STENIO ] No , sweetie .
[ STENIO ] Daddy had a problem , but it 's over now .
[ EDSON ] Why were you in the police car ?
[ STENIO ] I 'll explain later . I 'll take a shower and ...
[ EDSON ] No ! Tell me now !
[ EDSON ] Why can you arrive in the police car and I can 't ?
[ EDSON ] You called me a criminal .
[ LARA ] Don 't say that . [ STENIO ] He 's right .
[ STENIO ] Listen , son ... [ EDSON ] Fuck that !
[ EDSON ] Everyone 's saying mom was a whore .
[ STENIO ] Shut up .
[ EDSON ] Besides being a son of a bitch , I 'm a son of a criminal !
[ STENIO ] Edson ...
[ CICA SCREAMS ]
[ LARA ] Edson , are you hurt ? Are you okay ?
[ LARA ] Easy . It 's okay . I 'll help you get up .
[ STENIO ] Edson .
[ LARA ] The kids are sleeping . I 'm leaving , okay ?
[ STENIO ] Lara .
[ STENIO ] I didn 't mean to hurt Edson , okay ?
[ LARA ] I understand you lost it ,
[ LARA ] that you 're suffering , but so are your kids .
[ STENIO ] I know . It seems like I don 't , but I know .
[ LARA ] Is anyone after you ? [ STENIO ] No , no .
[ LARA ] I just want to know if I should worry about being here .
[ LARA ] I 'm worried about the kids .
[ STENIO ] I 'll take care of you .
[ LARA ] Good night . [ STENIO ] Good night .
[ STENIO ] I wanted you to handle food and drinks .
[ STENIO ] It 's Saturday at 3 : 30pm .
[ STENIO ] So what if it 's the day after tomorrow , Doraci ?
[ STENIO ] I want cake , brigadeiro , coxinha and everything .
[ STENIO ] Oh , and 11 candles , too .
[ STENIO ] Okay then . Okay . Thank you . Thanks , thanks .
[ STENIO ] Let me see this here .
[ STENIO ] Hand this out at school .
[ STENIO ] Saturday , 3 : 30pm . It 's your birthday .
[ STENIO ] Let 's celebrate and have a party .
[ EDSON ] My birthday is in September . [ STENIO ] I know . We 're anticipating it .
[ STENIO ] We 're having a party on Saturday .
[ STENIO ] Cica !
[ STENIO ] Here . Cica , here you go .
[ CICA ] What 's this ?
[ STENIO ] A party on Saturday . It 's Batata 's birthday .
[ CICA ] But his birthday ... [ EDSON ] I already told him .
[ STENIO ] But you two are so bummed about it !
[ STENIO ] Give it here . I 'll hand them out . I 'll invite people .
[ STENIO ] Get ready . On Saturday , we 'll have a ball .
[ STENIO ] We 're gonna rock it . Let me call everyone .
MUSIC
[ LAUGHTER ]
[ STENIO ] Lara . [ LARA ] Thank you !
[ STENIO ] Cica , Cica ! Lara !
[ STENIO ] Where 's Edson ?
[ LARA ] Where 's Edson ? [ STENIO ] Call him . Edson !
[ STENIO ] Edson !
[ STENIO ] Come here ! Bring the boys !
[ EDSON ] Okay !
[ STENIO ] Edson ! Is he coming ?
[ STENIO ] Look !
[ CELEBRATION ] [ CLAPPING ]
[ EDSON ] Thanks ! [ STENIO ] You wanted that , right ?
[ STENIO ] There you go !
[ EDSON ] Get off !
[ STENIO ] Open it ! Let 's assemble it together .
[ CHILDREN SCREAMING ] TENSE MUSIC
[ STENIO ] What 's wrong , son ?
[ VALDIR ] What did you do , StÃ © nio ?
[ STENIO ] Son , I didn 't know about this .
[ STENIO ] Son ! Son !
[ STENIO ] Excuse me , excuse me .
[ TOILET FLUSH ]
[ DOOR OPENING ]
[ STENIO ] Capela .
[ STENIO ] Can I talk to you ? [ CAPELA ] Go ahead .
[ STENIO ] If I gave you some money , would you get me some things ?
[ CAPELA ] Things ? What things ?
[ STENIO ] Pills . [ CAPELA ] What 's up ?
[ CAPELA ] I don 't understand it .
[ CAPELA ] GouvÃ © a is the doctor . Why are you asking me ?
[ STENIO ] Fuck it , Capela .
[ STENIO ] Do you think I never looked in the glove compartment ?
[ CAPELA ] The water is rising , right ?
[ CAPELA ] That 's the night shift .
[ CAPELA ] The guy 's mind gets screwed up .
[ STENIO ] I need something to get wired .
[ STENIO ] I 'm saying things , forgetting things ...
[ CAPELA ] Yes , I know . Stupid things , right ?
[ CAPELA ] Like leaving a body part in a gift box .
[ CAPELA ] Huh ? Valdir told me .
[ CAPELA ] The pill I should give you is a slap on the face .
[ STENIO ] You have no idea what I 'm going through .
[ CAPELA ] You know what I think ? You shouldn 't work here anymore .
[ FAR TV SOUND ]
[ GLASS BREAKING ]
SUSPENSE MUSIC
[ METALLIC SOUND ]
TENSE MUSIC
[ STENIO ] Ouch !
[ STENIO ] Odete !
[ STENIO ] Odete , get out of there !
[ STENIO ] Cica ! Edson !
[ STENIO ] Ouch !
[ STENIO SCREAMING ]
[ EDSON ] Dad ?
[ EDSON ] Dad ! [ STENIO ] Cica !
[ STENIO ] Kite wire ! Kite wire !
[ EDSON ] Dad ?
[ CUTLERY NOISES ]
[ STENIO ] I 'm already fine .
[ STENIO ] I cut myself , but it 's okay now .
[ STENIO ] It 's okay now . Thank God , right ?
[ STENIO ] I swear I didn 't mean any harm .
[ HIT ] [ SCREAM ] [ STENIO ] I 'm your father !
[ STENIO ] Can 't you talk to me ?
[ STENIO ] Edson ! [ CICA ] Excuse me .
[ STENIO ] I 'm sorry ... [ LARA ] Let them be , StÃ © nio . It 's better .
[ LARA ] They 're scared .
[ STENIO ] It 's unfair . I didn 't want them to get hurt .
[ STENIO ] I didn 't want them to get cut .
[ LARA ] What are you talking about ?
[ STENIO ] I was trying to protect them . But she ...
[ STENIO ] How does she do this ? [ LARA ] She ?
[ STENIO ] Odete .
[ LARA ] What did she do ? What did Odete do ?
[ LARA ] Did you do that ?
[ LARA ] I think you 're very stressed .
[ STENIO ] You 're right .
[ STENIO ] Odete 's dead .
[ STENIO ] I 'm not ...
[ STENIO ] I 'm not keeping it together .
[ LARA ] StÃ © nio , you need to be organized .
[ STENIO ] I 'm trying ! I 'm taking care of myself !
[ LARA ] Okay .
[ LARA ] So calm down .
[ THUNDER ]
[ STENIO ] Shit .
[ ODETE ] StÃ © nio .
[ THUNDER ]
[ ODETE ] StÃ © nio !
[ ODETE ] StÃ © nio .
[ ODETE ] StÃ © nio . [ DOOR CREAKING ]
SUSPENSE MUSIC
[ ODETE ] StÃ © nio .
[ STENIO ] Odete ?
[ STENIO ] Odete , what can I do ? What do you want ?
[ STENIO ] Do you want me to put a bullet through my head ?
[ STENIO ] If Cica and Edson ... [ ODETE ] That girl in my house .
[ ODETE ] I want you to bleed her for me .
[ STENIO ] Why ? I made the mistakes . If it 's blood you want ...
[ ODETE ] My kids will know who you are .
[ ODETE ] Kill her and I 'll go away .
[ ODETE ] If you don 't kill her , I 'll take my children .
TENSE MUSIC
[ STENIO ] I can 't .
[ ODETE ] No ?
[ ODETE ] You can 't , StÃ © nio ?
[ ODETE ] Haven 't you killed already ?
TENSE MUSIC [ THUNDER ]
[ ODETE ] Murderer ...
[ STENIO ] Lara .
[ LARA ] StÃ © nio ... Don 't do that .
[ STENIO ] What about the kids ?
[ LARA ] They 're inside .
[ STENIO ] Sit down .
[ LARA ] What 's going on ?
[ STENIO ] Nothing , for now .
[ STENIO ] But I think it 's going to happen .
[ LARA ] You 're scaring me .
[ STENIO ] I don 't want you to be scared of me .
[ STENIO ] You 're right . I need to pull myself together .
[ SIGHING ]
[ LARA ] Those things you said about Odete ...
[ LARA ] I don 't believe in that .
[ LARA ] I believe in God .
[ LARA ] Those who believe in God know the devil exists , too .
[ LARA ] You 're being oppressed . Let me take you to my church .
[ LARA ] My minister can help you .
[ STENIO ] If you really want to help me ,
[ STENIO ] take Cica and Edson out of the house for a few days .
[ STENIO ] There 's a shadow in my way . Only I can deal with it .
[ STENIO ] Take the kids to your house , please .
[ EDSON ] Cica .
[ EDSON ] Cica , wake up .
SUSPENSE MUSIC
[ EDSON ] Come .
TENSE MUSIC
HORROR MUSIC
[ CICA ] What is it ? [ EDSON ] Over there .
[ EDSON ] Open it .
[ EDSON ] It 's cool .
[ CICA ] Edson ?
[ NOISE ] [ CICA SCREAMING ]
TENSE MUSIC
[ CICA ] Lara !
[ SCREAMING ]
[ LARA ] Cica ? [ CICA ] Lara !
[ CICA ] Lara ! [ LARA ] Cica !
[ EDSON ] Cica !
[ LARA COUGHING ] Grab Cica !
[ EDSON ] Look at me ! Look at me , Cica ! Wake up !
[ NOISE ]
[ EDSON MAKING A NOISE ]
[ KNOCKING ON DOOR ]
[ EDSON ] Dad !
[ PANTING ]
[ STENIO ] Come in .
[ DISTANT BARKING ]
[ NOISES ]
TENSE MUSIC
BLEED
[ PHONE VIBRATING ]
[ LARA ] Hello . Hi , Doctor .
[ LARA ] What 's wrong ?
[ LARA ] I 'm here , I 'm here . I 'm sorry .
[ LARA ] Yes . I 'm on my way to the hospital .
[ LARA ] Thank you .
[ STENIO ] Lara .
[ LARA ] I need to go to the hospital .
[ CRYING ]
[ LARA 'S MOTHER ] I want my daughter far away from you .
[ LARA 'S MOTHER ] On this side , you are damned .
[ LARA 'S MOTHER ] And your wife won 't rest until you shed blood .
[ STENIO ] I 'm sorry .
[ LARA 'S MOTHER ] Your disgrace is already affecting your kids .
[ LARA 'S MOTHER ] But it won 't come near my daughter .
[ LARA 'S MOTHER ] Stay away from her . Do you promise ?
[ DOCTOR ] Excuse me .
[ DOCTOR ] Good morning . [ LARA ] Good morning .
[ DOCTOR ] I 'm from the department that deals with the deceased .
[ DOCTOR ] I need to talk to you to explain the release of the body .
[ STENIO ] I swear .
[ STENIO ] I 'm not a murderer .
[ LARA 'S MOTHER ] You have to erase this whore 's marks .
[ LARA 'S MOTHER ] Nothing that was Odete 's can be left behind .
[ LARA 'S MOTHER ] Nothing that reminds of here . Nothing she can cling to .
[ LARA 'S MOTHER ] Get rid of it all . Go !
SUSPENSE MUSIC
[ NOISE ]
[ RADIO TUNING ]
[ STENIO ] A guy from Vila Gustavo .
[ STENIO ] He had a mess with Sujo . His name is Jaime .
[ STENIO ] This rat from the store .
[ STENIO ] deserves to die like your deceased father .
[ STENIO ] Stabbed three times in the chest and thrown off a bridge .
TENSE MUSIC
[ FIRE CRACKLING ]
[ ODETE SCREAMING ]
[ SCREAMS ]
SUSPENSE MUSIC
[ CARTOON ]
[ STENIO ] Good night .
[ BIRDS SINGING ]
SUSPENSE MUSIC
[ STENIO ] Son , Son ! Where 's Lara ?
[ STENIO ] Where 's Lara ?
[ EDSON ] Isn 't she in your room ?
[ STENIO ] No .
[ RECORDING ] Your call is being forwarded ...
[ CICA ] Did Lara leave , Dad ?
[ STENIO ] Can 't you begin the search ?
[ STENIO ] No ... 24 hours ?
[ STENIO ] What if she 's in danger ?
[ STENIO ] Please , make this urgent .
[ KNOCKING ON DOOR ]
[ STENIO ] Okay , okay , okay ... I 'll call tomorrow .
[ VALDIR ] Do you know if she has a family we can call ?
[ VALDIR ] I 'll get the papers to begin the process .
[ STENIO ] Lara .
[ STENIO ] Talk to me .
[ LARA BREATHING ]
[ LARA ] StÃ © nio ?
[ LARA ] What happened ?
[ LARA ] Where am I ?
[ VALDIR ] You 're in the morgue , lady .
[ SCREAMS ]
[ VALDIR ] Hold her tongue !
[ VALDIR ] Hold her fucking tongue !
[ STENIO ] So ?
[ GOUVEA ] She 's stable .
[ GOUVEA ] We checked her temperature , her blood pressure ...
[ GOUVEA ] She 's going to be okay .
[ STENIO ] She almost died . Shouldn 't she go to the hospital ?
[ PARAMEDICS ] Right . We took a look at Valdir 's report .
[ PARAMEDICS ] You can look , if you want . I think he filled it out wrong .
[ PARAMEDICS ] It says she came in with respiratory failure ,
[ PARAMEDICS ] no heartbeat , a temperature of 937 ...
[ PARAMEDICS ] She was supposed to be dead .
[ GOUVEA ] StÃ © nio , this girl had a catalepsy .
[ GOUVEA ] It 's rare , but it happens .
[ PARAMEDICS ] Now there 's nothing we can do . Better take her home .
[ PARAMEDICS ] Let 's go .
[ GOUVEA ] Thank you .
[ STENIO ] There 's a sandwich here . There 's juice in the fridge ...
[ STENIO ] At 10 : 30 p.m. , you give her the pill , okay ?
[ STENIO ] The most important thing ... [ EDSON ] Don 't open the door . 1 Know .
[ STENIO ] That 's right .
[ EDSON ] Dad , she doesn 't recognize us .
[ EDSON ] I 'm worried about being alone with her .
[ STENIO ] Cica , turn down the TV !
[ STENIO ] She 's going to be okay . You don 't need to worry .
[ STENIO ] If she doesn 't know who you are ,
[ STENIO ] be nice to her .
[ STENIO ] That 's it .
[ STENIO ] Cica , turn down the TV ! Lara is sleeping !
SUSPENSE MUSIC
[ CELL PHONE RINGING ]
[ STENIO ] Hello . [ CRYING ]
[ STENIO ] Who is this ?
[ LARA ] StÃ © nio . [ STENIO ] Lara ?
[ LARA ] Come back home . [ STENIO ] Lara , are you okay ?
[ STENIO ] Has something happened ?
[ CRYING ]
It 's so good to see the truck
coming up the road
it 's so good when our love comes back
again
and again .
SUSPENSE MUSIC
[ STENIO ] Lara ?
[ THUNDER ]
[ STENIO ] Wait .
[ LARA ] Come .
[ THUNDER ]
[ STENIO ] Easy !
[ MOANING ]
[ THUNDER ]
[ SLAP SOUND ]
[ STENIO ] Lara ...
[ LAUGHTER ]
[ STENIO ] Lara .
[ STENIO ] Stop that .
[ ODETE ] Kill her .
[ ODETE ] Otherwise no one lives in this house .
[ STENIO ] Don 't do this , Odete .
[ ODETE ] Kill her !
[ GRUNTING ]
[ ODETE 'S VOICE ] Make the bitch bleed .
[ ODETE 'S VOICE ] Make her bleed .
[ ODETE 'S VOICE ] Your kids will know who you really are .
[ ODETE 'S VOICE ] You worm !
[ CICA ] Mom ?
[ CICA ] Don 't hurt dad !
[ EDSON SCREAMS ] [ HARD SOUND ]
[ CICA ] Dad !
[ GROANING ]
[ ODETE 'S VOICE ] I 'm your mother , you fucking brat !
[ ODETE ] People in the street are right .
[ ODETE ] You need discipline . [ EDSON ] No !
[ ODETE SCREAMS ] [ STENIO SCREAMS ]
[ THUD ]
[ STENIO ] Come on , Edson . Come on , Cica ! Go ! Go !
[ STENIO ] Shit !
[ EDSON ] Dad ...
[ STENIO ] The stairs . Go , go , go !
[ GROANING ]
[ EDSON ] Dad ...
[ EDSON ] Lara ... What was that ?
[ EDSON CRYING ]
[ STENIO ] Son , it was your mom in Lara 's body .
[ EDSON ] Shut up , you liar !
[ EDSON ] You piece of shit ! Don 't lie to me !
[ EDSON ] Don 't lie to me ...
[ CRYING ]
[ STENIO ] Let 's go downstairs .
[ LOUD NOISE ] [ SCREAMING ]
[ STENIO ] Under the stairs ! Under the stairs !
[ STENIO ] Odete , look at your kids .
[ ODETE ] Today they 're staying with their mother .
[ EDSON SCREAMS ]
[ EDSON ] Dad !
[ CICA ] Dad !
[ CICA ] Dad ! [ EDSON ] Dad !
[ GROANING ]
[ SCREAM ]
[ THUD ]
[ FIGHT NOISES ]
[ CRACK ] [ SCREAM ]
[ SCREAMS OF PAIN ]
[ LARA CRYING ]
[ LARA ] What happened here ? What happened ?
[ LARA ] What did you do ?
[ EDSON ] Lara ? [ CICA ] Lara ?
[ LARA ] Cica ... Edson ... Are you guys okay ?
[ STENIO ] She was here .
[ STENIO ] She was in your body .
[ LARA ] No . No .
[ LARA ] You 're crazy .
[ LARA ] Don 't come close !
[ ODETE ] I can wait . I have time .
[ STENIO ] Shut up ! [ CICA SCREAMS ]
[ ODETE ] You erased me like dirt .
[ STENIO ] I know , Odete .
[ STENIO ] I 'm not running away anymore .
[ LARA ] Is she here ?
[ STENIO ] God won 't forgive anyone who Kills their own family .
[ STENIO ] I killed Odete and Jaime .
[ STENIO ] There 's no forgiveness . [ LARA ] No ...
[ LARA ] Everyone knows who killed them .
[ STENIO ] But no one knows who had them killed .
[ LARA ] No ... You didn 't do that .
[ EDSON ] Dad ?
[ STENIO ] I did it , son .
[ STENIO ] But you ...
[ STENIO ] You 're not coming here anymore .
[ STENIO ] You 're not coming back because I 'm leaving .
[ STENIO ] It 's over , Odete .
[ STENIO ] It 's over .
[ SCREAMS ]
[ LOUD NOISE ]
[ LARA ] Go away ! Get out ! Go away !
[ STENIO ] They only have you now , Lara .
[ LARA ] No ! Cica , don 't ! Edson , stay ! [ EDSON ] Dad !
[ LARA ] Stay here ! Easy ! [ CICA ] Dad !
[ LARA ] It 's going to be okay !
[ LARA ] Stay here ! [ CICA ] Dad ! Come back !
[ EDSON ] Dad ! Dad ! Dad !
SUSPENSE MUSIC
[ STENIO ] Let 's go .
SAD MUSIC